# **Brandon Vicchiollo**

# **Full Stack Web Developer**

Fort Worth, TX 76134 vicchiollo.brandon@gmail.com (540)779-3301

Highly self-motivated Full Stack Web Developer that has strong knowledge of Javascript, Python, Django, Flask, HTML, CSS. Strong communications skills as well as works very well with others. Developing with these languages for 1-2 years. Open to learning new languages or systems. Accepts criticism and learns from it. Will be a great asset to your team!

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

#### Manager

Letara American Grill - Haslet, TX January 2019 to Present

- Trained new servers, host, food runners, and bartenders
- · Assured customer satisfaction at all times
- · Handled day-to-day operations
- Supervised 5 employees
- Managed shifts
- Paid out employees using payroll system for hourly employees
- Paid out servers with cash/checks
- Organized reservations above 40 people

#### **Customer Service/Server**

Riscky's BAR-B-Q - Fort Worth, TX March 2018 to March 2019

- Resolved all customer complaints in a professional manner while prioritizing customer satisfaction
- Shared best practices for sales and customer service with other team members to help improve the store's efficiency
- Developed reputation as an efficient service provider with high levels of accuracy
- Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and empathetic manner.
- Developed and maintained positive working relationships with others to reach business goals.
- Received beverage orders from wait staff and delivered beverages to guests.
- Maintained high standards of cleanliness and sanitation
- Greeted guests in a timely and professional manner
- Processed orders on a computerized Point of Sale system
- · Served each guest with a sincere, positive, pleasant and enthusiastic attitude
- Guided guests through menus while demonstrating thorough knowledge of the food, beverages and ingredients

## **Commercial Sales Representative ( Uber & Lyft)**

GEICO Corporate Office - Dallas, TX

January 2017 to June 2018

- Sell commercial insurance policies to businesses by using confidence, expert advice, and tailoring to the customer's needs.
- Interview prospective clients to obtain data about their financial resources and needs and to discuss any existing coverage.
- Ensure that policy requirements are fulfilled, insurance ID cards are appropriately e-mailed to all clients.
- Explain features, advantages and disadvantages of various coverage's to up-sell limits and additional coverage's.
- Run motor vehicle and clue reports, calculate premiums and establish payment methods.
- Provide customers with commercial policies for auto, TNC Ride share auto policies, general liability, professional liability and surety bonds.
- Provide clients with certificate of insurance to include additional insured's, waiver's of subrogation, contractual liability and hired/non owned coverage.

#### **Senior Office Assistant**

Wright Performance Horses August 2014 to December 2016

- Responsible for creating PowerPoint slides, Excel spreadsheets and Word documents.
- Developed orientation and training programs for clients
- Responsible for planning, coordination and implement multiple small to medium-sized projects.
- Send riding specific mailings to riding staff and horses in training
- Keep detailed records of training and assessment of horses.
- Submit orders for equipment and supplies, including feed, shavings and medicine, when needed, ensuring timely arrival of materials.
- Responsible for phone and email correspondence with members and prospective members
- Coordinates scheduling and oversees appointments with farrier, dentist and veterinarian
- Keep records on all horses and riders participating in riding program
- Responsible for scheduling all training programs and coordinating month end billing with all clients
- Evaluate current season and make suggestions for following season

#### **Education**

#### Trade School in Full stack Web development

Coding Dojo - Dallas, TX February 2020 to June 2020

#### **High School Diploma**

Azle High school - Azle, TX 2012

#### Skills

- Payroll
- Operations
- Inventory
- Scheduling

- training
- Web Development
- SQL
- AJAX
- HTML5
- APIs
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- MySQL
- Node.js
- JSON
- React
- Angular (1 year)
- MongoDB
- User Interface (UI)
- GitHub

## Additional Information

- Strong interpersonal skills
- Strategic account development
- Revenue and profit maximization
- Resolution-oriented
- Exceptional communication skills
- Pro-active and detail-oriented
- Ability to work with minimal supervision
- Excellent organizational, multi-tasking and time management skills
- Strong customer service skills
- · Advanced problem solving
- Dedicated team player
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- Computer skills and knowledge of office software packages
- Strong knowledge of Javascript, Python, Django, Flask, HTML, CSS.